It's now the morning chime! I, Ayaka Yasumoto, am attendance number 5 at Private Ebisu Junior High School.
It's time for the Stada Gamers Club, which has begun.
This time, continuing from last time, I would like to play the second episode of Tsugu no Hi.
Last time, I didn't know when to say "caw",
This time, I would like to say "Kyaa" immediately and promptly.
I would like to start now.
Here we go.
You are talking a lot, aren't you?
I have a feeling that the sound will scare you this time.
I have a feeling I'm going to be frightened.
What? I'm afraid it might attract psychic phenomena.
I can't be responsible for that.
Here.
It's done.
Look, it's not good.
It's a red ground. Look, it's not good.
It's in red.
You know, in the first episode.
You know, in the first episode, they...
They did that to me.
What do you call it?
He's really spinning.
They were giving me a lot of leeway.
What's that?
Oh, my God!
Oh, she's responding!
She's reacting to my caw!
I wonder what they've done to the character now.
I'm a girl now.
Well, let's go.
Let's go home early.
A girl's place
If you were a boy before...
You mean he's gone?
There he is.
That's it, right?
This is the one I'm going in with...
It's a ghost, isn't it?
It's not him.
Wrong guy.
Okay...
Oh, this is... this is the wrong person. All right, everybody, let's get going, because by the time this second episode is over...
Caw's...
By the time this second episode is over, the quality of Carr's will have improved to the point where...
I'm going to sleep.
Caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw-caw.
Is that a capo point?
I've got a cackle point.
Cackle cackle cackle cackle cackle
Okay, okay.
I can't play this reflex game for the life of me.
I think it's about to come.
Oh, oh... I've already done a lot of cans instead of cans.
I've been doing a lot of things...
I'm not playing "I'll take care of you," but "I'll take care of you. It's funny.
I'm going to go out with a bang.
It's about time. It's getting closer.
Oh, my God! That's the one I was talking about!
What the hell!
What's that?
Oh, it's a woman.
Where are you going?
My brother won't get a job.
Now's not the time to worry about that.
Hey, hey, hey!
I'm too embarrassed to invite my friends over.
My brother's...
Now is not the time to be worrying about your brother.
You're in danger.
See, the world is getting distorted
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
What's that supposed to mean? What's that supposed to mean?
Ha-ha-ha-ha! I'm sorry I said that.
Wait, are you coming back to do something?
I'll come back for more.
Oh, Enter?
Oh, hey, who's there?
Is there someone in there?
Oh, I think it's Care Point.
I'm going to spin around.
Cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle.
Cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle.
Cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle, cackle
Cary, Cary, Cary, Cary, Cary, Cary, Cary, Cary, Cary, Cary, Cary.
Cackle! No! No!
No! I don't know if this is your brother or not, but he's here to laugh at your outfit, so I put it on. I'm here to laugh at your outfit, so I put it on because you said you'd wear it.
Well, you sure are beautiful, aren't you, you idiot?
Wait! Behind you! Behind you! Behind you!
He's looking at me!
That's creepy. That was creepy too.
I flew away, big brother! Oh, brother... What? Huh?
Huh?
Okay, okay, let's go home.
I mean, aren't you worried about your brother? "Let's go home," big brother?
Oh, I'm done. Hey, aren't you trying to get away with a little bit of this game?
What's up with your outfit?
But I think you got the point more than you did in the first episode. I hope I can gradually get used to the charactor in this way.
I'm still curious about this outfit of your brother's.
I wonder what happened to your brother after this.
I wonder if it has something to do with the boy from earlier.
You mean the second episode?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, here it comes again.
I think it's coming back.
Caw... I'm not a cat on a horse that I can't hold you in.
I'm not a cat on a horse that I can't hold you in
I'm not a cat on a horse That I can't hold you in, your turn
Wait, wait, wait. What is this game?
What's going on?
What? No, no, no, help!
Hey, hey, hey.
Okay, so...
My brother keeps asking me for help.
But you don't help him.
In the second episode, you don't help him.
Shut up already.
I'd like to end.
Thank you very much.
Shut up!